Sh... Sorry.
Do you got any dehydrated mango, ginger?
Jicama, perhaps?
Nah.
Hmm.
This place sucks.
How much for that hat?
And this?
Ten dollars.
Bet.
Oh. Look at you.
♪ Sweet little girl ♪
♪ You know your baby loves you ♪
♪ Your love is driving
me crazy, crazy, crazy ♪
♪ Sweet little girl... ♪
♪ Girl, I'm in love...
Hello?
Hey, yeah, um, I'm here for the pickup.
Thank you.
Wow. I should probably... yeah.
Okay.
Hello?
Um, I'm here for the... the, uh, pick...
Was that Mr. Wonder?
In the car?
Oh, yeah.
Music of My Mind.
Masterpiece.
I love Stevie.
Yeah, me, too.
I-I like to, uh, listen
to it on long drives
because, uh, his songs
are long, you know?
Yes.
I'm Darius.
Apologies.
I'm Theodore Perkins.
Please... call me Teddy.
Come on. Please, come sit in the parlor.
Oh, cool. I've never been in
a house with a parlor before.
Would you like a glass of water?
Yeah.
Kind of parched.
Darius would like a glass of
water when you have a moment.
Would you like some?
What is that?
It's a soft-boiled ostrich egg.
It's called an owl's casket.
Nah, I'm good.
So...
you're here about the piano.
How did you hear about it?
Um...
someone posted on the
biohacking message board
saying their boss had a
multicolored key piano.
Trying to get rid of it. Free of charge.
Sam. Was it Sam?
My audiovisual woman.
Uh, we don't use real names on
the message boards so, so maybe?
Hmm. Oops.
Are you a music lover?
Yeah. Yeah, I consider myself... yeah.
I work with a friend
of mine. He's a rapper.
Rap.
There's a funny one.
I found it never quite
grew out of its adolescence.
No, I wouldn't say that.
You know, we got Jay-Z. He's, like, 65.
But don't you find it
insufficient as an art form?
Nah, I think, you know,
every now and again,
people just want to have a good time.
Good time.
Hmm.
How long have you played?
Oh, you...
you're talking about the piano.
Uh, nah, I never studied.
I just, uh, kind of
like the way it looks,
especially this one
with the colored keys.
Are you a fan of Benny's?
Who?
Benny Hope.
The pianist.
He's the one who owned the piano.
He's my brother.
Oh, sh-shit! Is that Keith Jarrett?
Yes.
- Let me look at that.
- Yes.
And Stevie, as well.
And Al Jarreau and Ahmad Jamal.
I think Nina's over there somewhere.
Ahmad and my brother,
they had a residency
in New York together.
Hmm. That's Flames, man.
Yes. Flames.
My-my brother and Ahmad,
they were staying at a-a hotel
in Brooklyn off of Bergen Street.
Eight dollars a night,
if you can believe it.
He told me something I'll never forget.
He said, "Your brother...
plays pain better than anyone."
Benny just played what he knew.
Is he, uh, no longer with us?
No, he's alive.
He lives here with me.
I take care of him.
He developed a rare skin condition.
Can no longer go in the sunlight.
Yeah. You see, I keep
it quite dark in here.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
He must get depressed.
It's not easy.
But who knows?
Maybe one day we'll get
a great album out of it.
A masterpiece.
Yeah. Righteous, brother.
Uh, your, uh, your butler or whatever,
they, um, didn't bring the water yet.
Oh, I don't have a butler.
I just use this to remember things.
Finish that hat for Dionne Warwick.
Wash your hands, immediately.
Darius would like a glass of water
when you have a moment.
Right then.
Excuse me.
This...
Yeah, I can't sit next to this. Mm-mm.
Mm.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
- Oh!
- Ooh!
What are you doing up here?
Uh, I-I just heard the piano.
It sounded great, so...
Shh, shh. Benny, he... he's sleeping.
He's very tired, um...
he needs his rest.
- You know?
- Okay.
- Uh-huh. Okay.
- Thank you.
Um, cool.
Do you... do you still want the water?
Oh... yeah.
I can bring it to you.
Downstairs.
Bottled or tap?
Uh... bottled, I guess.
Oh. Bottled.
I'll bring it... I have Fiji, and Evian.
I'll mix it with some Poland Springs.
Maybe a Voss?
Okay.
No, I'll see you downstairs.
But I just wanted to ask...
Okay.
Why the fuck you still there?
Look, man, I really,
really want this piano, man.
It's nice.
There's colored keys. And it's free.
But is you willing to
die for it, though, man?
I mean, he sound like a serial killer.
And let me get a five cheese
Krystal combo, no fries.
It's cheaper with fries.
No fries.
That's rich nigga shit, man.
You don't know nothing about that.
Look, man, if I leave, I'll regret it.
And I got a two regret life limit pact.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
A what?
A two regret life limit pact.
Somebody got to take
me out if I go over two.
What? How would anyone know
you went over two regrets?
I'd tell them.
- Look...
- Oh, shit.
Paper Boi!
I mean, the dude is
obviously a weirdo, man.
Look, now just play along with it,
get the piano, get the hell up out.
Yeah, but how, though, man?
I feel like...
like he stalling or something.
Like he want to keep me here.
Explain it again, man.
Is Teddy the white
dude or the black dude?
You know what? I don't even
think Teddy exists, bro.
I feel like Benny created
Teddy to make up for the fact
that he made himself look like a ghoul.
A ghoul?
I mean, how bad is it?
It's real bad, man.
I mean, bad.
The nigga look like somebody
left Sammy Sosa in the dryer.
Sammy Sosa?
Yeah. Skin bleaching?
Look, have somebody type in, um,
"Sammy Sosa hat" in Google image search.
Hey, man, look, man.
Sometimes, people come
over, they want a quarter,
and they feel like they
can sit and chat and shit.
But other people, you
know what I'm saying, like,
they want an eighth, they pay
me, and they get the hell on.
- Can I take a flick? To Laurence.
- Look, man...
- Say happy birthday, Laurence.
- That's how I know
- that I'm simply a conduit...
- This nigga gonna stunt on me
- with the new iPhone.
- between them and their weed.
See, keep gunning, and
he ain't got no choice
but to make clear what he want from you.
I see what you're saying.
I see, I see what you're...
you're saying be unequivocally honest
to make a healthy transaction.
Wow, man, you know what?
You keep this up, you could
be the next Steve Harvey, bro.
Steve Harvey, nigga? No, no, no.
I'm-I'm like Dr. Phil,
you know what I'm saying?
- Yo.
- Hell, that, that nigga stay caked up.
- Yo! Shit!
- What the...?
Oh, shit! Oh!
- What happened?
- Yo!
Yo, why this nigga the same
color as his fucking hat?
Yeah, man, this nigga looks
like a white man's penis.
Yo, man,
why this nigga look like
what's under a scab, though?
- Goddamn.
- Oh, God.
Peace, man.
All right, peace.
Oh, God.
Put some extra fries in there.
Take them out.
Just don't eat them, damn.
Man.
Hmm.
Ugh.
Surprise.
Shit. Yeah, I'm not a big photo person.
Apologies.
Um, this is yours, anyway.
I got you your water.
Oh, yes, thank you.
I needed that.
Hmm.
Oh. That's cool.
Feel free to take any of it.
Yeah.
What is this place, man?
It's a gift shop.
I designed it myself to
feel... like a trophy room.
More in the motif of the museum.
Oh, wait, so you're turning
this whole place into a museum?
Yes. I've already started the process
of making this a historical site.
You're actually the first
person to be in here.
Feel free to Twitter
or blogspot any of it.
Uh, you know what, actually,
I'm kind of in a rush, uh...
May I show you something? Um...
I-I promise to get you your piano.
I... I really think you'll
like what I have in store.
Sure.
What's in there?
Go ahead.
Walk in.
Okay.
Hey, uh, Teddy?
Uh...
This is my favorite part of the museum.
What the hell is this?
This is my father.
He's the reason for all of this.
When me and Benny were children,
he instituted a very
rigorous training method.
Piano three hours a day,
twice a day.
With exams on Sundays,
that, if failed,
meant physical punishment.
He wanted the best out of us.
It's because of him we have all of this.
So you said your dad,
uh, used to beat you
so you'd be good at piano?
To be good at life.
We were his sacrifice.
Oh. Well, um, I'm not trying
to, like, shit on your
dad, or nothing, man,
but that seems a little... unnecessary.
Most people wouldn't understand.
To make an omelet, you
have to break a few eggs.
I mean, to build bridges,
people have to fall.
Are you not mad at your dad?
Of course not.
There was no way for a child
to understand what was at stake.
He just wanted the best for us.
My father used to say,
"Great things come from great pain."
I want this wing of the museum
to be dedicated to great fathers.
My father, Joe Jackson,
Marvin Gay Sr....
Tiger Woods's father,
Serena Williams's father,
- _
- the father that drops off
Emilio Estevez in The Breakfast Club.
Hey, uh, look, I...
I'd like to make this transaction
as efficient as possible.
So is there any documents I got to sign?
For tax purposes?
Of course.
Uh...
Ted?
Sure, um, sorry I can't,
uh, thank Benny himself,
personally, man.
Don't be.
The disease is very advanced,
and he doesn't like
people seeing him that way.
It's a very hard thing.
Yeah.
- I can imagine...
- No, you can't!
You have no idea.
Sign the highlighted parts.
I have to go turn on the elevator.
When it arrives,
place the piano on it.
I'll wait for you in the lobby.
Okay, well, thanks...
All right, what is this?
The hell?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Back.
All right.
Fine, destiny.
Shh.
_
Okay. What do you want me to do?
Come on. Are you serious?
Uh...
But why can't, why can't
you just get the gun?
All right. All right.
I'll go get your gun,
but I got to put my piano
in the car first, okay?
So you stay here.
And I'll be back with your... gun.
Why would he say that, though?
I don't even know, bro.
This dude crazy, bruh.
He want me to kill him,
this dude way past depressed.
This whole situation's just been weird
since I got here.
Yep. Fuck this shit, bro.
Look, I got the piano.
Now I'm just gonna get
the hell up out of...
Let me call you back, bro.
Hey. Hey, Teddy!
Your car is blocking mine.
Teddy?
Come on, Benny, put something into it.
Posture.
Posture. Keep your form.
Don't you cry.
Again!
- I love this song.
- Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Something wrong?
Uh...
Watch your form.
Yeah. You-you, uh, parked your
car right in front of mine.
Oh.
I'll move it.
Um...
Anything else?
Uh, where's your, uh, bath-bathroom?
It's up the stairs.
Third door on your left.
Okay.
Right next to the attic.
I was just up there myself.
Do you know what I found?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, man. Chill, chill.
Congratulations.
For-for what?
I choose you.
You're my sacrifice.
Put your phone on the ground.
No.
Keep that.
I want it to look real.
Want what to look real?
The home invasion.
You killed Benny because
you were obsessed.
No, man. You...
Look, there is no
fucking Benny, all right?
Exactly.
Sit in the chair.
Put them on.
Ankles first.
You know, uh, not all great things
come from great pain.
Sometimes it's love.
Not everything's a sacrifice.
Sacrifices are necessary, Darius.
Yeah, maybe.
But your dad should have said sorry.
I'm sorry.
Shit.
I went through daddy shit myself.
But when you're young,
you try to just...
make it be okay and say
everything's gonna be fine.
And that's just,
you don't know the difference, but...
that don't give you an excuse to grow up
and repeat the same shit over and over.
It's like there's a,
there's a "what if" factor.
What if you would have been
great at something else?
Or if you would have seen the love...
instead of all the other
shit like, like Stevie.
I'm sorry?
Stevie Wonder.
Stevie had his own... sacrifices.
He was blind.
Yeah, but he wasn't blinded.
He saw through his music.
That's beautiful...
but wrong.
Benny.
You're alive.
Shit.
Fuck.
Benny, uh, look. I'm sorry that you
had to go through what
you had to go through, man.
It...
What?
Oh.
Wait, Benny, what are
you, what are you do...?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait. Oh, shit!
Oh! Fuck.
Oh, shit. Goddamn it.
Ugh.
Fuck.
Synced and corrected by Octavia
- www.addic7ed.com -